Santiago Ardanuy

 ${\bf \diamondsuit}$ Spain ${\bf \boxtimes}$ santiagoardanuyhamill@gmail.com ${\bf \nwarrow}$ 649 553 796 ${\bf \mathscr{S}}$ Showcase Portafolio

in Santiago Ardanuy Hamill 🕠 salty3r

Introduction

I'm a full-stack developer with a background in videogame design. I've been working with **Cibernova**, a business that develops AI RAG systems with a particular emphasis on **marketing and customer service**. My expertise spans across various technologies and frameworks, allowing me to contribute effectively to complex software projects.

Experience

Software Developer

Valencia, Spain (Remote) Jan 2024 - Present

Cibernova

• Developed a SaaS providing virtual employees to clients using Next.js, AWS, and microservice platforms like n8n, Google Cloud, and Azure.

- o Built AI assistants in WhatsApp, Facebook and WWW.
- Implemented and optimized RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) systems for enhanced AI performance.
- Fine-tuned AI models for specific business needs, improving accuracy and relevance of responses.
- Created customized n8n workflows for small businesses, automating processes and integrating various tools.
- Developed WordPress solutions tailored for smaller businesses, enhancing their online presence.

English Language Teacher

Kids &Us

Montornès del Vallès, Catalonia, Spain Sept 2022 – June 2023

3D Scenario Artist

Playable Dreams Studios

Hospitalet de Llobregat, Catalonia, Spain Oct 2021 – Apr 2022

Education

Grupo Atrium

Sept 2023 - June 2024

Master's in Web Development, Computer Engineering

- Development of B2B and B2C applications.
- Training in best practices for SEO, Front-End, Back-end, Databases, and web deployment.

Universitat de Barcelona

Sept 2018 - June 2022

Degree in Video Game Creation and Applied Games, Video Game Design and Interactive Content.

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect

Oct 2023

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

DevOPS Culture and Mindset

Oct 2023

Sept 2023

University of California, Davis

Google IT Support Professional Certificate

Google

Languages

Fluent: Spanish, English, Catalan

Basic: Italian, German